Now, can you write a function that accepts an array of strings as an argument and
والآن، أيمكنكم كتابة دالة تستقبل مصفوفة من السلاسل كوسيطة
searches in that array to find the longest string inside it?
وتبحث في داخل تلك المصفوفة عن أطول سلسلة داخلها؟
Your function should look something like this,
ينبغي أن تبدو الدالة شبيهة بهذه:
public String findLongestName and then it
public String findLongestName،
accepts a parameter which is an array of strings called names.
ثم تستقبل معلمة وهي عبارة عن مصفوفة من سلاسل نصية تسمى names.
Inside your function, the first thing you want to
داخل الدالة، أول ما عليكم فعله
do is get the size of your array or the length of your array,
هو معرفة حجم المصفوفة أو طولها،
so that you can use this for your loop condition.
بحيث يمكنكم استخدامه في حالة حلقتكم.
And then you want to create a loop that visits every single cell in this array and
ثم عليكم إنشاء حلقة تمر على كل خلية في هذه المصفوفة
compares the length of the string inside
وتقارن طول السلسلة النصية داخل تلك الخلية
Remember to initialize the longest string to the very first item in the array as well.
تذكروا أن تعيّنوا متغيّر longestString لأول عنصر في المصفوفة أيضأً.
For example, if the names array was something like this,
مثلاً، إذا كانت مصفوفة names بهذا الشكل،
then when you calculate the size of the array,
فعند حساب حجم المصفوفة،
you should get 10.
يجب أن يكون الناتج 10.
You should initialize your longest name string variable to the very first one,
ينبغي عليكم تعيين متغيّر longestName الذي من نوع string مع العنصر الأول،
and then you should create a loop that visits every cell and
ثم عليكم إنشاء حلقة تمر على كل خلية
compares the length of each of those strings to the longest one that you have.
وتقارن طول كل واحدة من هذه السلاسل مع أطول سلسلة لديكم.
If it is longer, then you update it to the new line.
فإذا كانت أطول منها، تقومون بتحديثها وتخزين الطول الجديد.
By the end of the function,
عندما تنهي الدالة عملها،
if that was the input,
إذا كانت هذه هي المدخلة،
you should get this name as your output.
فينبغي أن تحصلوا على هذا الاسم كنتيجة.
Remember that, to get the length of a string,
تذكروا أنه لإيجاد طول سلسلة ما
you use the.length function,
عليكم استخدام دالة length.،
whatever string that is,
أياً كانت تلك السلسلة،
which can also be a cell in the array.
والتي قد تكون خلية في المصفوفة أيضاً.